Now, let's look at how we will instill redundancy in server-based services.
现在 让我们来看看我们如何在基于服务器的服务中实现冗余
For multi availability zone redundancy,
对于多可用性区域冗余
you will need to configure a subnet group.
您将需要配置子网组
A subnet group consists of
子网组由
more than one subnet in which the server is comprised of instances.
一个以上的子网 服务器由实例组成
A subnet is associated with only one availability zone.
子网仅与一个可用性区域相关联
So to create a subnet group to support a multi availability zone configuration,
因此 要创建子网组以支持多可用性区域配置
your subnet group should include subnets from multiple availability zones.
子网组应该包含来自多个可用性区域的子网
If you run one instance of an application and
如果您运行应用程序的一个实例 并且
the underlying hardware fails or the availability zone fails,
底层硬件失败或可用性区域失败
your service will become unavailable until
您的服务将变为不可用
a new server can be created in a different availability zone.
可以在不同的可用性区域中创建新的服务器
The time this will take depends on the service and the amount of data that you have.
此时间将取决于您拥有的服务和数据量
Also, depending on the service,
另外 根据服务的不同
you may lose some data.
你可能会失去一些数据
To reduce downtime to seconds you need to create multiple instances.
要将停机时间缩短为秒 您需要创建多个实例
This takes different forms in different services.
这在不同的服务中采用不同的形式
In ElastiCache, you configure a cluster.
在 ElastiCache中 配置集群
In RDS, you choose a multi-AZ configuration.
在 RDS 中 选择多 AZ 配置
The goal in all cases is to create a hot standby that
所有情况下的目标是创建一个热备用
has a current copy of your data ready to take over at a moment's notice.
您的数据的当前副本已准备就绪 可随时接管
Yes, sometimes this is all as simple as a checkbox.
是的 有时这就像一个复选框一样简单
RDS has a create multi-AZ checkbox that will
RDS 具有创建多 AZ 复选框 将
create a secondary instance for you with no other effort on your part.
为您创建辅助实例 但不需要其他工作
Multi-region redundancy for server-based services is not always easy.
基于服务器的服务的多区域冗余并不总是容易的
Some services such as RDS allow you to create a read replica in another region,
某些服务 ( 如 RDS ) 允许您在其他区域创建读副本
but you'll have to intervene to switch your platform to use it as a primary database.
但您必须进行干预以切换平台以将其用作主数据库
Other services don't actually have any multi-region support.
其他服务实际上没有任何多区域支持
Elasticsearch, for example, does not have
例如  elasticsearch 没有
provisions for running in a multi-region configuration.
用于在多区域配置中运行的规定
In these cases a common approach is to move backups of the data from
在这些情况下 通用方法是将数据的备份从
these services into other regions so
这些服务进入其他区域
that the service could be recovered there if necessary.
在必要时可以在那里恢复服务
Redundancy for these services is not cheap.
这些服务的冗余度并不便宜
To have redundant server,
要有冗余服务器
you basically pay double the cost.
你要付出双倍的代价
Depending on the service,
根据服务的不同
you may not even be able to use that secondary instance.
您甚至可能无法使用该辅助实例
It will just sit there waiting just in case you ever need it.
只要你有需要的时候它就坐在那里等着
This may not sound like a great value proposition,
这听起来可能不是很有价值的命题
but it is the same situation you'd be in if you're running in a data center.
但如果你在数据中心内运行 就会出现同样的情况
The only way you have highly available mySQL is if you have two servers.
您拥有高可用性 mySQL 的唯一方法是您有两个服务器
Often the technologies we run at AWS are dictated by the needs of our applications.
我们在 AWS 上运行的技术往往取决于我们应用程序的需求
When this is the case,
如果是这样的话
services like RDS make a lot of sense and still provide substantial value.
RDS 这样的服务有很多意义 仍然提供了巨大的价值
Later, we will study other AWS native services that offer
稍后 我们将研究其他 AWS 本机服务提供
a better pricing model for multi availability zone and multi-region redundancy.
为多可用性区域和多区域冗余提供更好的定价模型